One family's journey from Down Under to center stage.
Unsung Hero is a drama, music, family film directed by Richard Ramsey.
When David Smallbone's successful music company collapses, he moves his family
from Australia to the United States in search of a brighter future.
With nothing more than their six children, their suitcases, and their love of music, David
and his pregnant wife Helen set out to rebuild their lives from the ground up.
Based on a remarkable true story, a mum's faith stands against all odds;
and inspires her husband and children to hold onto theirs.
David Smallbone, played by Joel Smallbone.
Helen Smallbone, played by Daisy Betts.
Rebecca Smallbone, played by Kirrilee Berger.
Eddie Degarmo, played by Jonathan Jackson.
Kay Albright, played by Candace Cameron Bure.
Grandpa James, played by Terry O'Quinn.
Unsung Hero is a 2024 American Christian drama film written and
directed by Richard Ramsey and Joel Smallbone.
It follows Rebecca, Joel, and Luke Smallbone of For King & Country and
their life journey to become Christian recording artists.
Unsung Hero was released in North America on April 26, 2024.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and
grossed $21.1 million  at the box office.
The film explores themes of australia, immigrant,
biography, based on true story, family.
The tone is emotional.